You big dummy.
Assaulting a police officer?
Still want to fight?
I was wrong. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Look at you.
You've gotten a lot stronger.
I heard you went from a small director
to a big one.
What do you think?
Do you think I'll
become a famous director first,
or you'll become the police captain first?
I'm working hard too.
Can't we do it at the same time?
You don't deserve it.
I do.
Let's eat.
How about this place?
This one is fine.
You're so tall.
Duck a little.
Li Xingchen,
Li Xingchen.
I have nothing left.
Are you sure you want to leave me?
I don't deserve to be a detective anymore.
Because of this,
we can't be friends anymore.
Take care.
I'm sorry.
Pull over.
Go.
Do you even know how to drive?
What did I do, officer?
Did you yield to the pedestrian just now?
Driver's license and vehicle registration.
I'm sorry,
officer.
I was in a bit of a hurry.
I don't think it's a big deal.
Please cut me
some slack.
I'll definitely be more careful next time.
I'll give you a pass this time.
Thank you, officer.
Off you go.
License plate C 73194.
This isn't right.
That traffic cop's uniform looks off, too.
And his hand signals
are wrong.
Hello, 110?
I want to make a report.
Hello.
Hello, ma'am.
I'm a police officer.
Can I ask you something?
Go ahead.
Is this tricycle yours?
No, it's not.
Not yours.
Do you know whose it is then?
I don't know.
Why are you asking?
Well,
this tricycle is blocking the road.
We have to take it back to our unit first.
I need to know whose it is
so I can return it,
right?
So you don't know?
I don't know.
This piece of junk
was probably abandoned.
Understood.
Thanks. That's all.
Okay.
Ping Fu'an.
Hello.
Have you seen this vehicle?
No, I haven't.
Okay. Thank you.
Never seen him.
Have you seen him?
Never seen him. No.
Okay, thanks.
Any luck?
Everyone here
says they haven't seen him.
Yeah.
That's weird.
They all denied seeing him.
None of them have seen him.
Something's definitely wrong.
That's a breakthrough.
It's worth looking into.
Hello?
Captain Li,
someone reported a fake traffic cop.
Copy that.
Let's go.
Do you see that guy?
He's gonna run as soon as he sees us.
Stay close on the bike.
Got it.
POLICE
Captain Li,
there's something wrong with those two.
See the one next to him?
Jiang, get the car ready.
Si, looks like the real police are here.
Should we run?
Freeze!
Take off your masks
and helmets.
That's right.
Just do as you're told.
Captain Li,
let's take them
back to the station.
Don't move.
Get up.
Let's go.
Oh my god.
It's bleeding.
Kid,
have some water.
You must be tired
after running for so long.
What are you looking at?
You think you're justified?
Look at you.
A big boy,
yet you bite people like a puppy.
Tell me.
Name.
Si.
Full name.
Bai Xiaosi.
The real name on your ID card. 045509.
The real name on your ID card.
That is my real name.
Bai.
ID number.
045509. You're only 17.
045509, you're still a minor.
My birthday is in a few days.
Besides,
you don't look much older than me. You...
17 years old.
You must be in school. Which one?
I dropped out a long time ago.
Take a look at this guy.
Is he the fake traffic cop
from that night?
Doesn't look like him.
Doesn't look like him,
or isn't him?
I can't be sure.
That night,
the man was wearing a mask.
Jiang,
put a mask on him.
Copy that, Captain Li.
Look over there.
Look here.
I'm sure.
It's not him.
You're that sure?
That man's eyes
slanted upwards,
kind of like phoenix eyes.
And
his eyelashes were very long.
You remember it that clearly?
Because only his eyes
were showing at the time.
I remember
there were raindrops clinging
to his eyelashes.
Got it.
Where were you between 7:00 and 8:00 p.m.
on October 23rd?
At a bar.
Which bar?
Du World,
the one at the west gate
of the Second Factory.
Can anyone prove it?
Of course.
It was my girlfriend's birthday
that night,
and several of her besties were there.
You have a girlfriend at 17?
What's wrong, officer?
It's not illegal, is it?
It's not.
Give me your girlfriend's name
and phone number.
Bai Xiaosi.
Where did you get this uniform?
Why are you impersonating a traffic cop?
Bai Xiaosi, right?
Let me tell you,
we strongly suspect
you're involved in a murder case.
If you really didn't do it,
come clean
and tell us everything you know.
Don't get yourself implicated, got it?
M-Murder?
I didn't do it.
I didn't do anything.
I-I just
impersonated a traffic cop
and shot some videos.
Tell the truth.
What was your motive?
It was just cosplay.
Bai Xiaosi,
you're really something.
You dressed up as a cop
and dared to direct traffic on the street.
Are you that shameless?
I've admired the police since I was a kid.
I feel so cool in a police uniform.
Then one time,
I went to a school gate to direct traffic,
just for kicks,
so I had my girlfriend record it
and post it online.
Hello,
Wenwen.
Did you see our video?
It went viral.
The view count is super high.
And there are so many comments.
I have to say, this trick really worked.
Is that it?
That's it.
Just so
the video could go viral?
Do you know how hard it is, officer?
If this post goes viral,
I'll become famous.
I'll have my own fans.
Do you guys know what fans are?
Captain Li,
we've been waiting
for you.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Sorry
for keeping you all waiting.
I'll drink three glasses
as an apology later, okay?
No need.
You're a captain now.
We understand you're busy.
Right, guys?
Deputy.
Just keeping busy.
Sit.
Alright, come on.
Classmates,
with Li Xingchen here,
everyone's present.
Come on, let's raise our glasses.
May our friendship last forever.
To our friendship.
Captain Li, stop looking.
Song Yanfei isn't here.
Xingchen,
you two were so close.
Hasn't he contacted you
these past few years?
No.
Come on,
for our second glass,
I wish all of us
more wealth,
better health,
and happier families.
Come on, cheers!
Alright, cheers!
Let's eat.
Come on.
Captain Li,
how is it?
Perfect timing, right?
Why are you here?
I figured you couldn't drive
after drinking,
so I went out to buy some stuff
and dropped by
to be your driver.
Is this your car?
Yours?
My dad's is mine.
Get in.
I heard
Song Yanfei is back in our city.
Who told you? Is it true?
It's true.
My wife saw him
at the Cultural Palace a few days ago.
But strangely,
when she said hi,
he ignored her.
Maybe he didn't hear her.
Alright,
I'm leaving.
Bye.
I heard you're back.
Aren't you going to say hi?
Captain
Li,
What is it?
I found Li Fang,
the organizer of
the dance competition.
Let's go see him.
That was fast.
Good job.
Captain Li,
are you
upset
about the
class reunion?
Was your first love not there,
or was she there
but you're not her fiancé?
Keep running your mouth.
By the way,
we need to see Gao Yayan tomorrow.
Go inform Wei.
Okay, okay.
Let's go.
I used to come to this cultural palace
when I was a kid.
It's still the same river.
Gao Yayan called me
and asked if it was okay to meet here.
I asked why.
She said she was accompanying
her boyfriend for a rehearsal here.
Rehearsal? What rehearsal?
I don't know.
Seems like a dance drama.
According to Gao Yayan,
her boyfriend seems to be an artist.
Something's wrong.
Gao Yayan
wasn't sad at all when her father
passed away last time.
And now she's in the mood to accompany
her boyfriend for a rehearsal.
Exactly.
When Wei asked her that day,
she overreacted.
I think Gao Yayan still has some clues.
Let's go. Let's go in.
Wait.
Why do I feel like I've seen
a dance drama with this theme
somewhere?
Officers, please come in.
Five, six, seven, go.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four, five, six.
Xiaoyu,
formation. Move in.
Right, remember it.
Let's do it again.
This is my boyfriend.
He's rehearsing a dance drama
called "Circle".
It's roughly about...
We all live in
different circles.
So we explore
whether this is the life
we chose for ourselves,
or if
we are actually living in
a circle drawn by others.
Okay.
Much better than the past two days.
And tomorrow, same time, same place.
All right.
Dismissed. Good work, everyone.
Good work.
Put your coats on. Put your coats on.
Put your coats on.
Is your dad picking you up today too?
Go on. Go find your dad.
Hurry up and put your coat on.
Li Xingchen Yu Xiaotong
Song Yanfei Wang Zhiyong (Wang Ruizi)
Shen Xi Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance (in order of
the number of strokes in their surnames)
Xiao Ze Wang Hao
Feng Shu Liu Yakun
Jiang Dahai Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Bai Sha Li Xintong
Mu Liyan Chen Yongxia
Weng Wei Huang Fei (Huang Jingxin)
Gao Yuhai Cao Haitao (Cao Jingshi)
Cast (in order of the number
of strokes in their surnames)
Forensic Doctor Cheng
Li Xingchen's Classmate Liu Haohan
Zhao Wenjuan Li Ziying
Investor Zha Minxin
Lead Singer Xu Weina
Xiao Ze's Mother Zhao Yue'en
Assistant Bai Zhihao
Li Xingchen's Mother Dong Dong
Zhao Wenjuan Li Ziying
Friend Xiao Ba Niu Dali
Yao Sha
Secretary Qian Duoduo
Woman Sun Meili
Girl Ying Ying Huang Mingfei
Fleeing Driver Liu Haohan
Liu Ran
Speaking Police Officer Wang Zhiguo
Mother Liu Li
Middle-aged Man Wang Xinda
Driver Lao Zhao Wei Hong
Locksmith Fu Wang
Xiao Ze's Father Zhou Wen
Xiao Ze's Mother Pei
Speaking Girl
Young Man Tang Yuye
Ren Jiefei
Female Secretary Qian Duoduo
Driver
Wounded Person Xu Ganggang
Crane Operator Liu Haitao
Company Head Bai Yongjun
Yan's Father Li Tianjun
Woman Liu Yutong
Male Doctor Wang Keming
Speaking Neighbor Wu Meiling
Speaking Contestant Nan Xi Xu Ziyi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in
Cashier
Forensic Doctor Zhou Wen Pei Xiao
Cleaner Liu Li
Receptionist Wang Yanmin
Extra Da Qing Liu Haohan
Receptionist Xiao Yu Ren Jiefei
Crew
Chief Presenter Xu Yue
Co-Presenters Feng Fei Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Planner Li Meina
Police Consultant / Original Story: Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producers: Sui Dalong, Gao Jingman
Producer
Production Manager
Unit Manager: Yin Zhongheng
Set Operations
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Vegetable Washer: Hu Xiuxia
Transportation Team
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Wang Jizhang, Xiong
Zhang Kai, Liang Hui
Wang Yiguo
Cao Yongjie
Directing Team
Executive Director: Sui Chenggong
Assistants to Director:
Tang Yuye, Li Gaoyang
Casting Coordinator: Kang Hairu
Casting Director: Dai Guoming
Sound Team
Sound Director
Sound Assistants: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Art & Props Team
Art Director: Zhao Daqian
Executive Art Director: Wang Wenqi
Props Master: Yang Xueshan
Props Team Leader: Sun Donghua
On-set Supervisor: Hou Yonghao
Set Dressers: Zhang Li, Zhang Qingzhong
On-set Deputy Supervisor
Camera Team
Camera A Operator: He Yong
Camera A Focus Puller: Yao Yonglei
Camera B Focus Puller: Li Chenlong
Camera C Operator: Ma Mingguo
Camera C Focus Puller: Xie Xiaozhong
Camera Assistants: Guo Ruicai, Liu Shihao
Lighting Director: Gao Yun
Lighting Assistants:
Zhang Xiaoguang, Chang Lin
Te Rigun
Styling Director: Gao Bin
Hair & Makeup: Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
On-set Hair & Makeup Supervisor: Li Zixu
On-set Wardrobe Supervisors:
Zhang Lei, Yi Junli
On-set Wardrobe:
Zhang Tingting, Qiu Yaqiong
Marketing & Distribution Team
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Planning Director: Yang Liuting
Project Coordinator: Zhao Zihan
Copywriters: Zhang Weirui, Li Ziwei
Video Editors: Wang Jiahui, Miao Wenbo
Graphic Designers: Ren Zhongjun, Shi Qi
Beijing Wenhui Qiming
Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-production Supervisor
End Credits: Jin Linxin
Re-recording Mixer: Zhang Kai
Ambience Editor: Zhang Xinyu
Sound Effects Editor: Zhang Xiaoman
VFX Production
Production Supervisor: Gao Dong
VFX Executive: Jin Linxin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Dafu
Music Coordinators:
Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Guitarist: Liu Zining
Cellist: Zi Long
Score Mixer: Zhao
Song Recording Studio:
Beijing Landuo Recording Studio
Songs
Lyrics by Yue Shunming
Composed by Xiao Zhuang
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
"Song of Spring"
Performed by Zhang Keying
Children's Vocals by Zhang Maolin
Lyrics by Yue Shunming
Arranged by Xiao Zhuang
Composed by Xiao Zhuang
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
Lyrics by Gao Jingman
Arranged by Wang Anyu
"Half a Beat Slow"
Lyrics by Fan Fan
"The More I Love, The More I'm Wrong"
Performed by Wang Weijia
Composed by Xiao Zhuang
Arranged by Zhao Yi
Performed by Liu Ruixun
Lyrics by Bai Yuxiang
Arranged by Zhao Yi
Produced by Xiao Zhuang
Special Thanks
Fangxian Lulingwang Liquor Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Sinopharm Dongfeng Huaguo Hospital
Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Jindian Marketing
Management Co., Ltd.
Weibo
Sina Entertainment, Weibo TV, Sina TV
Co-production Companies
Co-presentation Companies
Shanxi Chengyi Film
and Television Media Co., Ltd.
Songyuan Senshengda Economic
and Trade Co., Ltd.